pitpass.com 2010-11-27

# pitpass - the latest, hottest F1, GP2, GP2 Asia & GP3 news

At **pitpass** we take privacy issues relating to users of our web site extremely seriously. We respect your personal information and will hold that information as required by Data Protection legislation.

The following privacy policy explains what information we will collect about you, how we will use it and the measures we will take to ensure that it is kept secure. If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the privacy practices of this site you can contact us at the email address below.

By using this web site you consent to us collecting and using personal information about you on the terms set out in this policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check back here regularly.

Like most websites **pitpass** uses cookies for collecting user information and the data collected in this way may be processed in the same way as other data submitted to **pitpass** and for the same purposes. A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your hard drive by your web browser. We use cookies so as to be able to build up a profile of your interests and preferences and this may be used by us to make your visits to our site more enjoyable.

**1: What information we collect**

Information related to your visit to this site (such as which pages you visit, how often you visit and which competitions you enter) and the information you supply when registering or when entering our competitions (such as your name and e-mail address) will be held and stored by us.

**2: How we will use your information**

We will use your information to supply you with the latest information on motor racing. Your information will help us improve the site and to help us design competitions that will most appeal to our users. We may supply statistics about the use of our site to third parties, but these statistics will not directly identify you. We will also use your information to tell you about any of our offers, products or services that we think might interest you.

Occasionally, we may send you targeted advertising and marketing messages on behalf of third parties. We may also share your information with reputable third parties whose products or services we think will really interest you and those third parties will get in touch with you directly to tell you about their products or services. If you do not wish us to use your information as set out in this paragraph you should click on 'No' in any relevant scroll boxes during the registration process or email us at the address below.

By supplying us with your information you confirm that you do not consider use of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy to be a breach of any of your rights under the Telecommunications (Data Protection and Privacy) Regulations 1999. You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your personal details and/or information concerning your activities whilst visiting this site, we shall do so.

**3: How we will keep your information secure**

Keeping your information secure is very important to us. We will use all reasonable measures to safeguard your data but please note that we cannot guarantee that any data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. To help us provide you with information relating to products and services that we think you will be interested in your data may from time to time be processed and held by third parties outside the European Economic Area. If your information changes or if you wish us to stop using your data at any time, you can email us at the address below.

Chris Balfe  
Editor
